const trigonometryQData = [{
    questiontext: "What formula can you use to find the length of a side of a right-angled triangle?",
    answer: "Pythagoras' Theorem",
    choices: ["Sine Rule", "Area of a triangle", "Cosine Rule", "Pythagoras' Theorem"]
}, {
    questiontext: "What method can you use to find the angle in a right-angled triangle?",
    answer: "SOHCAHTOA",
    choices: ["Pythagoras' Theorem", "SOHCAHTOA", "Area of a triangle", "Cosine Rule"]
}, {
    questiontext: "If the Sine Value of an angle is positive, which two quadrants will the angles be located?",
    answer: "1st and 2nd",
    choices: ["1st and 2nd", "1st and 3rd", "1st and 4th", "1st Only"]
}, {
    questiontext: "What angle betwen 0 and 90 degrees has the same Sine and Cosine value?",
    answer: "30",
    choices: ["30", "90", "60", "45"]
}];

const algebraQData = [{
    topic: "algebra",
    questiontext: "What does HCF stand for?",
    answer: "Highest Common Factor",
    choices: ["Hypothetical Common Fact", "Highest Cumulative Form", "Highest Common Factor", "Hypotenuse Change Face"]
}, {
    topic: "algebra",
    questiontext: "The order of operations in Maths is? ",
    answer: "BIRDMAS",
    choices: ["BIRDMAS", "Multiply, Divide, Add, Subtract", "What you need to type into calculator", "As they appear on the page"]
}, {
    topic: "algebra",
    questiontext: "The -b formula is use to find what?",
    answer: "Roots of a quadratic",
    choices: ["Length of a line segment", "Factors", "The square root of a number", "Roots of a quadratic"]
}, {
    topic: "algebra",
    questiontext: "If you divide any number by 0, what answer do you get?",
    answer: "Cannot divide a number by 0",
    choices: ["Cannot divide a number by 0", "0", "1", "the number"]
}];

const geometryQData = [{
    questiontext: "The four angles in a quadrilateral add up to how many degrees?",
    answer: "360",
    choices: ["180", "260", "360", "400"]
}, {
    questiontext: "An angle between 0 and 90 degrees is called?",
    answer: "Acute",
    choices: ["Acute", "Obtuse", "Reflex", "Straight"]
}, {
    questiontext: "Points that are on the same line are called?",
    answer: "Collinear",
    choices: ["Parallel", "Perpendicular", "Coplanar", "Collinear"]
}, {
    questiontext: "An axiom is a...?",
    answer: "Statement we accept to be true",
    choices: ["The axes of a graph", "Statement we accept to be true", "Mathematical mystery", "The reverse of a theorem"]
}];

const statisticsQData = [{
    questiontext: "SSSWhat does HCF stand for?",
    answer: "Highest Common Factor",
    choices: ["Hypothetical Common Fact", "Highest Cumulative Form", "Highest Common Factor", "Hypotenuse Change Face"]
}, {
    questiontext: "The order of operations in Maths is? ",
    answer: "BIRDMAS",
    choices: ["BIRDMAS", "Multiply, Divide, Add, Subtract", "What you need to type into calculator", "As they appear on the page"]
}, {
    questiontext: "The -b formula is use to find what?",
    answer: "Roots of a quadratic",
    choices: ["Length of a line segment", "Factors", "The square root of a number", "Roots of a quadratic"]
}, {
    questiontext: "If you divide any number by 0, what answer do you get?",
    answer: "Cannot divide a number by 0",
    choices: ["Cannot divide a number by 0", "0", "1", "the number"]
}];